Contact

+923322757575 (Home) engrrakesh@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/engrrakesh (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Multisim

Matlab

Proteus

Leading E&I Department @ PepsiCo Beverages.

Tharparkar District

Summary

A diligent, creative and enthusiastic professional with experience in developing innovative concepts for designing electrical systems. Possess excellent problem-solving skills coupled with a positive attitude towards life which enables me to excel in different environments and work under stressful conditions with tight deadlines.

Experience

Haidri Beverages Pvt. Ltd. PepsiCola International Franchise Lead E&I

February 2022 - Present (2 months)

Islamabad, Islāmābād, Pakistan

Electrical & Instrumentation Department

Unifood Industries Ltd Lead Technical & Projects Department October 2019 - February 2022 (2 years 5 months) Balochistan, Pakistan

Engineering & Projects Department

Lotte Kolson (Pvt.) Limited Asst. Manager E&I Department September 2015 - October 2019 (4 years 2 months) Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

Electronics & Instrumentation Department

Hilal Foods (Pvt) Ltd.

Executive E&I Department

May 2013 - August 2015 (2 years 4 months)

Pakistan

Electrical & Instrumentation Department

Gourmet foods dubai Sr. Executive Engineer August 2014 - September 2014 (2 months) Dubai, United Arab Emirates

Siemens

Engineering Trainee
January 2013 - April 2013 (4 months)

Pakistan

Energy Service Department

ZOOM CONSULTANCY LTD

Junior Engineer August 2011 - December 2012 (1 year 5 months) Karachi, Pakistan

Education

Shaheed Zulfikar Ali Bhutto Institute of Science and Technology Master of Science - MS, Project Management · (September 2020 - January 2022)

NED University of Engineering and Technology Bachelor of Engineering (B.E.), Industrial Electronics · (2006 - 2010)